in the last lecture we downloaded
在上一节课中我们下载了
inkscape version 1.2
Inkscape 1.2版
ainscape version 1.3 however has big
然而，Aainscape 1.3版有很大的
improvements like the shape Builder tool
形状构建器工具等改进
so I downloaded the latest development
所以我下载了最新的发展
version from the inkscape website by
来自Inkscape网站的版本由
going to download latest development
正在下载最新发展
version
版本
this version may still have some bugs in
此版本可能仍有一些错误
it but I find it already very stable
但是我发现它已经很稳定了
when you open inkscape for the first
当您第一次打开Inkscape时
time you're welcomed by a quick setup
欢迎您快速设置的时间
screen
筛网
you can do some settings here but you
你可以在这里做一些设置，但你
can also do that later
以后也可以这样做
I downloaded inkscape version 1.3 which
我下载了Inkscape 1.3版
will soon be the current version
将很快成为当前版本
if you don't want to go through the tabs
如果您不想查看选项卡
you can exit the welcome screen at the
您可以在以下位置退出欢迎屏幕
top right
右上角
and when you press escape the welcome
当你按下逃逸欢迎键
screen will not show up anymore when you
当您执行以下操作时，屏幕将不再显示
open inkscape now let's look at how you
打开Inkscape现在让我们看看你是如何
can customize the user interface I will
可以定制的用户界面我会
do this by showing how I created mine at
通过展示我是如何在
the right I have fill and stroke layers
右边我有填充层和描边层
path effects and the swatches panel to
路径效果和色板面板
add a panel click on the Arrow
添加面板单击箭头
I can change the order of the panels and
我可以更改面板的顺序和
I can drag a panel to another place
我可以将面板拖到另一个地方
to get more room I can collapse the
为了得到更多的空间，我可以把
panels by clicking on the three dots
通过单击三个圆点来选择面板
and I can get the panels below more room
我可以把电池板放在更大的空间下面
by dragging the three dots in the
通过将三个点拖入
document properties I have made the
文档属性，我已将
canvas called desk darker by setting
画布通过设置称为桌面更暗
lightness to 30. then I went to file
将亮度设置为30。然后我去申请了
save template I called it A4 dark desk
保存模板我叫它A4暗桌
and selected set as default template in
并在中选择设置为默认模板
the view menu I hit the commands bar and
查看菜单I点击命令栏和
the palette colors that normally show at
调色板颜色通常显示在
the bottom
底部
I also prefer to work in full screen
我也更喜欢全屏工作
mode to get maximum space in the height
模式以在高度中获得最大空间
under edit preferences windows I chose
在我选择的编辑首选项窗口下
remember last Windows geometry this
记住上一个Windows几何图形
means that when I change something in my
意思是当我改变我的
UI these changes are saved here you can
UI这些更改保存在此处，您可以
also choose to see the welcome screen
还可以选择查看欢迎屏幕
when you start inkscape under theming I
当您在主题下启动Inkscape时
have the high contrast inverse theme and
具有高对比度的反向主题，
multi-color icons
多色图标
you can change the colors of these icons
您可以更改这些图标的颜色
if you want
如果你想
and if you have a high resolution screen
如果您有高分辨率屏幕
under toolbars you can increase the size
在收件箱下您可以增加大小
of the icons at the left and at the top
左侧和顶部的图标
in the next lecture we will start
下一节课我们将开始
creating shapes
创建形状